Hunter K. Miller

3330 Bexley Dr, Colorado Springs, CO 80922 Phone: 719-482-4153 Email: hkmiller16@gmail.com

Summary

Proactive problem-solver with over six years of experience in a rapidly changing environment, participating in and managing the installation and maintenance of data networks in tactical and business settings, as well as experienced holding an extracurricular leadership and personnel management position.

Experience

Hardware Support, TEKsystems, subcontracted to Harris

February 2016 - Present

Hardware Support Technician

Provide level 1, 2, and 3 technical support for a broad range of Information Technology Equipment (ITE), including computers, printers, and scanners in a 1000+ user environment.

- Support several different models of desktop computer, laptops, and multifunction devices.
- Work with the Service Desk to resolve tickets fully and in a timely manner.
- Support set-up, maintenance, and tear down of training events ranging from 2 to 70+ computers across multiple classification enclaves.
- Work with hardware team to image and deploy 100+ machines across multiple enclaves to support Tech Refresh or Break-Fix requests.
- Perform duties of an Equipment Control Officer (ECO). Duties include managing the transfer of accountable
 equipment between ITE accounts, managing ITE inventories, and proper removal of ITE from the Air Force
 Equipment Management System(AFEMS)
- Perform duties required of Hardware Service Asset and Configuration Manager (SACM). Duties include
 creating requests to purchase ITE, starting process to add items to the Hardware catalog, and working with users
 to determine what ITE is needed to satisfy their requirement.

End User Services, Pikes Peak Library District

September 2014 - February 2016

End User Support Technician

Provide first response triage and troubleshooting to 500+ staff and public users in a business environment, as well as manage and completed projects assigned to me through a ticketing system.

- Managed and supported over 500,000 patrons using public computers in multiple locations
- Imaged and deployed 100+ staff and patron computers as well as manage hardware related to the assigned role, as well as managed their user accounts and privileges using Active Directory
- Provided first response to problems with management systems and servers serving the district
- Effective time management and project prioritization with little to no supervision
- Performed regular routine and preventative maintenance on job-specific hardware and software as required.

Samsung Technical Support, Alorica, Inc.

May 2014-September 2014

Level 1 Technical Support Agent

Diagnose, troubleshoot and educate clients on mobile devices remotely from a call center environment. Interfaced with clients to document problem, explain warranty, and create repair orders for devices with hardware malfunctions.

- Successfully handle and document 25 or more calls a day with various problems ranging from data network configurations to damaged hardware.
- Acquired and retained in depth knowledge of multiple products and their troubleshooting methods.
- Constantly using effective time management and prioritization skills to increase customer satisfaction results.
- Demonstrated ability to effectively handle complex customer issues in an independent, timely and efficient manner while maintaining quality standards for customer satisfaction

United States Marine Corps, Sergeant

August 2009-May 2014

Data Network Specialist (March 2010-May 2014)

Installed, configured and managed data network systems in both stand-alone and client-server environments. Planned and implemented the integration of multiple information systems in a network environment.

- Maintained and administrated for computer networks and related computing environments including computer hardware, applications, and network device configurations.
- Managed a team at a computer help desk, providing support to over 200 users, performing tasks such as data backups, networks troubleshooting, and hardware troubleshooting.
- Employed best practices in rapidly changing settings, both in logical configuring and educating customers in policies and standard procedures.

Training Non-Commissioned Officer (Nov 2012 - Jan 2014)

Plan, direct, and coordinate training and education activities for members of an organization.

- Provided leadership and training to over 50 personnel.
- Supervised and evaluated instructor performance of training programs, providing feedback for improvement.
- Managed and organized training needs of individuals under my charge using software like Microsoft Excel.

Education

Communication-Electronic School

Trains Marines in ground electronics maintenance, tactical communications, and air control/anti-air warfare operations and maintenance in order to ensure commanders at all levels within the Marine Corps have the ability to exercise command and control throughout the operational environment.

Actively pursuing a Bachelor's degree in Information Systems from University of Colorado, Colorado Springs

Personal Skills

Secret Clearance, Security + Certified, ITIL Certified, Win 10 Configuring Certified, Personnel management, Communication, Fast Learner, Stress management, Capable problem solver, Detail oriented, Windows proficiency, Logistics, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint, Leadership, Instructor Capable, First Aid, Self-Motivated